"危险"
"爆炸撼动校园"
"卡尔弗大学发生神秘事件"
"有人目击绿色怪物"
"发现实验室设备"
"嫌犯逃逸"
"有人目击绿色大脚怪"
"武器征用要求: 核准 史氏工业"
"班纳试图联络罗丝博士"
"追捕行动继续"
"毒眼-神盾局长"
"关系人:罗斯博士"
"他不再逃亡了吗?"
"五个月没有出现"
距离上次变身-第158天
巴西荷欣尼亚贫民区
熟了吗?
Is it ready?
葡英字典
艾迪的老爹先生
打得好
Hey! That's a great punch.
饿肚子?
饿肚子
你要练习控制呼吸
这里是掌控情绪
恐惧是不好的 所以要控制情绪
Fear no good. So emotion and control.
利用你的横膈膜
想要控制你的怒气
就要控制你的身体
控制你的脉搏
呼吸
Breathe.
等一下
Wait.
好
Okay.
这只是暂时修好 你需要...
I can make it work for a while, but you need...
我需要一间新工厂
好 好
Okay. Okay.
这五个月来你一直在帮我
你太聪明 不该当临时工
让我正式雇用你
关掉!快关掉!
Shut that off! Turn it off!
小心!
Watch out!
好了
Okay!
出口国- 美国
你想跟我吃午饭吗?
滚开 臭老外
你想找麻烦吗?
不想
太迟了
不要让我...饿肚子
你不会喜欢我...
饿肚子
我用错字了
That's not right.
太好了
Oh, you.
看到没?看到吗? 我可以离开这鬼地方了
You see that? See that? My ticket out of here.
加密中-呼叫蓝生生
蓝 你在吗?
绿先生 很高兴你打来
蓝先生:我神秘的朋友 真高兴又跟你连络上!
我找到了
终于!
那种花很美吧?
务必要注射高剂量 祝好运
可恶
Damn it!
又一次失败
你用了多少?
全部
我们该见面了
不安全
伽玛辐射感染很危险
别再找花了
寄血液样本给我
要不然我就帮不了你
绿先生
蓝先生 纽约市
维吉尼亚州阿灵顿
这个你也许有兴趣
Here's something a bit more interesting.
罗丝将军
我们怀疑是伽玛中毒 密尔瓦基市
It's a possible gamma sickness. Milwaukee.
有人喝了一瓶瓜拿纳果汽水
A man drank one of those guarana sodas.
结果比他想像的更带劲
Guess it had a little more kick than he was looking for.
- 汽水在哪里装瓶? - 波尔图港 巴西
- Where was it bottled? - Porto Verde, Brazil.
派人到装瓶工厂找一个白人
Have our people look for a white man at the bottling plant.
先按兵不动 要是被他看到他就会逃走
Tell them no contact! If he even sees them, he's gone!
强生堡 佛州沼泽地
我替你找到最顶尖的士兵
I got you who I could. Short notice, but they're all quality.
其中有一个王牌
And I pulled you one ace.
伊密布朗斯基 俄国出生 英国长大
Emil Blonsky. Born in Russia, raised in England.
从皇家陆战队借调到特种部队
And on loan to SOCOM from the Royal Marines.
我知道你动用了些人脉
I know you cashed in some chips for this, Joe.
我很乐意帮忙 祝你任务成功
Glad I could help. Just make it good.
这是目标和位置 这是逮捕行动 生擒活捉
This is the target and the location. Snatch and grab, live capture.
你们要用麻醉枪
You'll have your dart clips and suppression ordnance,
非不得已才能开枪
but live fire is for backup only.
警方会协助 但不能打草惊蛇
We got local out there, but we want it tight and quiet.
他会反抗吗?
Is he a fighter?
目标是躲避美国政府的逃犯
Your target is a fugitive from the US government
他窃取军事机密
who stole military secrets.
也涉嫌杀害两名科学家
He is also implicated in the deaths of two scientists,
一名军官一名爱达荷州州警 以及两名加拿大猎人
a military officer, an Idaho state trooper and possibly two Canadian hunters.
所以别等他反抗
So don't wait to see if he's a fighter!
把他麻醉然后带他回来
Tranq him and bring him back.
有来电- 好消息
初步验血显示伽玛量明显减少
可以治好我吗?
可以
不过我需要更多资料
拜托
Oh, come on.
细胞感染程度- 伽玛浓度
不可能- 资料不在这里
在哪里?
家里
针孔摄影机
Camera.
看到了
Here we go.
把那只狗赶走
Get rid of the damn dog.
抓住他!
Take him!
目标在逃逸
Target's on the move.
他在哪里?
Where is he?
地面
He's on the ground.
- 上吧! - 上吧!
- Let's go! - Go!
快点!
Move, move!
谢谢你
快...快...
Go, go, go!
开车!
Go! Go!
把人群赶走
Clear everyone out!
别追丢他
Do not lose him!
哦 不
Oh! No!
紧跟在他后面
Get around behind him!
目标经过090机动车
Target moving past mobile unit 0-9-0.
不是吧
Oh, no.
别开玩笑
You got to be kidding me.
- 他在哪里? - 看到目标
- Where is he? - Target acquired.
臭老外
Gringo!
一起滚!
Let's go.
不
No!
拜托 住手
Please! No!
我的电脑
Not the computer!
还给我
Gimme that! No!
耍不了狠了吧?
再来功夫那套呀
请你住手
当我...生气...
会很坏
你生气会很坏?我生气才会很坏
You bad angry, G? I very bad angry.
噢 不
Oh, no.
马上就会发生很糟的事
You don't understand! Something really bad is about to happen here!
没错 你会遭殃
有人看到吗?
Anybody else seeing this?
有一个不明物体
We've got a bogey of some kind. Please advice.
那就是目标 使用麻醉枪
That is the target! Use every tranq you've got!
快点
Do it now!
用真枪!用真枪!
Go live! Go live! Go live!
- 走 - 离开这里!
- Move!- Get out of the way!
不!
No!
它在后面 快走
It's behind us! Move! Move!
快开枪
Get him!
开枪
Shoot!
离...我...远点
Leave me alone.
不!不!
No! No!
开枪前我就知道事情不对
I knew something was different before I got the shot off.
他逃走时留下这个
He had it on him when he bolted.
这是他女友?她在帮他?
Is that a girlfriend? She helps him, maybe?
她不再是个问题
She is no longer a factor.
他们早就失联 他是一个人
We closed that door to him a long time ago. He's alone.
他也想要离群索居 不过查查看他有和谁联络
He wants to be alone. But see if he's been talking to anybody.
恕我冒昧
Forgive me, sir?
没有人想谈谈刚才的事吗?
Doesn't anybody want to talk about what went down in there? 'Cause...
不是他甩掉我们
He didn't lose us.
他也不是一个人
And he was not alone, sir. We had him.
我们把他困住了 只是后来被攻击
And then something hit us, something...
一个很大的东西
Something big hit us!
它把堆高机当作垒球丢
It threw a forklift truck like it was a softball!
它是我见过力量最强大的东西
It was the most powerful thing I've ever seen.
它不见了
Well, it's gone.
要是班纳知道那是什么
Well, if Banner knows what it is,
我会逮到他
I'm gonna track him down, I'm gonna put my foot on his throat
- 逼他说出... - 那就是班纳
- and I'm gonna... - That was Banner.
它...
It
就是班纳
was Banner.
- 你必须解释清楚 长官 - 我不必解释
- You have to explain that statement, sir. - No, I don't.
你表现得很好
You've done a good job.
收拾好就带队上飞机 我们要回家
Pack up and get our men on a plane. We're going home.
距离上次变身-第1天
停车
Wait.
拜托
Please.
你能帮忙吗?
我不会说葡萄牙话
我在哪里?
Where am I?
瓜地马拉
我要去下一个城镇
你能帮我吗?
上车
来 披着
你要去哪里?
回家
我以前出任务也出过差错
I've run into bad situations on crap missions before.
同袍因为
I've seen good men go down
事先不知情白白牺牲
purely because someone didn't let us know what we were walking into.
但我是军人 必须继续战斗
I've moved on to the next one, because that's what we do, right?
这是我们的天职
I mean, that's the job.
但是这玩意?
But this?
这件事太诡异了
This is a whole new level of weird.
我不能就这样撒手不管
And I don't feel inclined to step away from it.
如果你要再去抓他 我要参一脚
So if you're taking another crack at him, I want in.
这次一定要事先准备好
And, with respect, you should be looking for a team that's prepped and ready to fight,
因为要是那玩意再出现
because if that thing shows up again,
最勇敢的军人也会被吓得尿裤子
you're gonna have a lot of professional tough guys pissing in their pants.
长官
Sir.
墨西哥恰帕斯
有没有更宽的裤子?
Tienes mas stretchy?
很好
Yeah. Perfecto.
我要告诉你的事非常敏感
Let me emphasise that what I'm about to share with you
对我和对军方都一样
is tremendously sensitive, both to me personally and the Army.
你应该知道美国的武器研发计划
You're aware that we've got an Infantry Weapons Development programme.
二次大战期间 他们进行新实验
Well, in WWII, they initiated a subprogram
生物科技力量增强实验
for Bio- Tech Force Enhancement.
打造超级大兵
Yeah, Super Soldier.
没错
Yes.
没这么简单 但是没错
An oversimplification, but yes.
我命令他们再度进行大胆实验
And I dusted it off, got 'em doing serious work again, bold work.
研发部只想制造更好的武器
Across the hall, they were trying to arm you better.
我们则想打造更强的士兵
We were tryin' to make you better.
班纳的实验只达到初步阶段 根本就还不能应用
Banner's work was very early phase. It wasn't even weapons application.
他以为他在研究抗辐射方法
He thought he was working on radiation resistance.
我从来没告诉他真相
I would never have told him what the project really was.
但他太有把握了 竟然私自进行人体实验
But he was so sure of what he was onto, that he tested it on himself.
结果出了大错
And something went very wrong.
或者是完全做对了
Or it went very right.
他的身体是属于美国军方的
As far as I'm concerned, that man's whole body is the property of the US Army.
你说他不是研发武器 对吧?
You said he wasn't working on weapons, right?
- 是的 - 但你是 是你 对吧?
- No. - But you were. You were, weren't you?
但是你们在进行别的实验
You were trying other things.
我们研发出一种
One serum we developed
很有潜力的血清
was very promising.
- 他为什么要逃亡? - 他是个科学家
- So why did he run? - He's a scientist.
不是军人
He is not one of us.
- 你几岁?45岁? - 39岁
- Blonsky, how old are you? 45? - 39.
- 打仗老得快 对吧? - 没错
- It takes a toll, doesn't it? - Yes, it does.
那就别再出任务
So get out of the trenches.
以你的记录 你可以当上校
You should be a Colonel by now, with your record.
不 我是战士 永远都是
No, I'm a fighter. I'll be one for as long as I can.
如果十年前的我有我现在的经验
You know, if I could take what I know now, put it in the body I had ten years ago,
我绝对不会跟我自己对决
that would be someone I wouldn't want to fight.
我可以让你变得更强
I could probably arrange something like that.
维吉尼亚州卡尔弗大学
距离上次变身-第17天
生物科学系大楼
伊莉莎白罗斯博士- 细胞生物学
史丹利比萨餐馆
保重了
Take care, kids.
打烊
史丹 我发誓
Stan, I give you my word,
有关我的谣言都不是真的
whatever you've heard about me, it's not true.
我知道 我一直都知道
Oh, I know it. I always knew it.
你也知道我跟你们俩的交情
I mean, you know how I felt about you two.
- 你去找过她吗? - 没有
- Have you talked to her? - No.
她不知道我在这里
She doesn't know that I'm here.
- 她有男友了? - 对 他是精神科医师
- She's with somebody? - Yeah, he's a head shrink.
听说是最顶尖的 好人一个
They say he's one of the best. But a really nice guy.
很好 那很好
Good. That's good.
- 布鲁斯 我能帮你什么忙? - 我需要地方住几晚
- Bruce, what can I do to help you? - I could use a bed for a few nights.
- 你可以用楼上的空房间 - 那真是太好了
- You can have the spare room upstairs. - That'd be so great.
还有另一件事
There is one other thing.
抱歉 不好意思
Excuse me. Pardon me.
借过
Coming through.
老兄 我要送比萨到五楼
Hey, pal. I got a delivery on five.
五楼没人了
I don't think there's anybody up there.
收不到钱我就惨了 拜托让我上去看看
Oh, man. I'm gonna catch hell if I don't collect. You got to let me try.
我多了一块比萨 我请客
I'll tell you what. I got an extra medium. Take it on the house.
- 你很上道 - 老天保佑你 兄弟
- You are the man. - God bless you, brother.
好
All right.
使用者帐号:罗斯博士
密码
好
Okay.
计划名称:伽玛脉冲 搜寻中
查无此资料
搜寻参数- B.班纳
加密纲
登入- 远端聊天
加密中- 呼叫蓝先生
绿先生 找到资料了吗?
资料不见了
没有资料...
我帮不上忙
现在怎么办?
我必须继续逃亡
我们打烊了 抱歉
We're pretty well closed here, folks. I'm sorry.
拜托 史丹 周五夜耶
Oh, come on, Stan. It's Friday night.
先说好
Oh, kids.
除了意大利干酱什么都没了
I got nothing but marinara now.
我一定要吃块比萨
Oh, I got to have a Mister Pink, please.
她忙着工作 又没吃晚饭
She worked through dinner again, of course.
史丹?
Stan?
我说:"你在哪里?
And he... I go, "So, yeah, I mean, where were you?
"我不知道你在哪里"
"I can't... I don't know where you were, Cecil."
他说:"我没在你那里"
And he goes, "Not where you been at."
我想 "噢 上帝啊" 感觉真是太糟了
I thought, "Oh, my God." I just felt so awful.
布鲁斯?
Bruce?
贝蒂?怎么了?
Betty? What's going on?
贝蒂...
Betty...
我看到的是不是真的?
Just tell me if I saw what I think I saw.
- 我不知道该说什么 - 拜托你说实话
- I don't know what to say. - Please, just tell me the truth.
别走 别走
Don't go. Don't go.
我要你跟我来
I want you to come with me now.
拜托 跟我来
Please. Come with me.
求求你
Please.
这是我们的资料
It's our data.
我趁他们把一切搬走前拿的
I got in there before they carted it all away.
希望有一天能找到解答
I hoped somewhere that it might tell us something someday.
- 将军知道这件事吗? - 应该不知道
- Does the General know that you have this? - No, I don't think so.
我有两年没跟他说话
I haven't spoken to him in a couple of years.
你一定要确定
You have to be sure.
为什么不能一起直接去找他?
Bruce, I don't understand why we can't just go in there together and talk to him.
他跟我说过他想做什么 他要取出我体内的细胞
He told me what he wanted to do. He wants it out of me.
进行分析后再复制它
He wants to dissect it so that he can replicate it.
让它成为武器
He wants to make it a weapon.
冷冻计划:增强武器
- 我猜你会想要... - 谢了
- I thought you might want to... - Thanks.
我最好早点走 愈早愈好
Listen, I should leave early, as early as I can.
真的?你不能待下来?
Really? You can't stay at all?
我很想 但是这里不安全
I want to, but it's just not safe for me to be here.
- 我能借点钱吗? - 当然了
- If I could borrow some cash... - Of course.
我得搭巴士
I need to take a bus.
至少让我陪你去车站
Well, at least let me walk you to the station.
好吧
Okay.
- 该有的都有了吗? - 晚安
- You have everything you need? - Yeah.
我
I...
什么
What?
晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
尽量休息吧
I hope you get some rest.
我们会替你注射最低剂量
We're giving you a very low dose only.
我要你保持专注听命行事
I need you sharp out there and disciplined.
只要出现副作用
First sign of any side effect,
我就喊停 等你恢复以后才能复职
we stop and you're off team until you straighten out.
- 同意吗? - 同意
- Agreed? - Agreed.
你要打两次针
You'll get two separate infusions.
一针打入深肌 一针打入骨髓
One into the deep muscle, one into the bone marrow centres.
第二针会很痛
The bone ones are going to hurt.
没事吧?
Is everything okay?
应该没事
I think so.
过来
Come here.
我帮你拉出来
- I just wanna do this. - Oh.
这样比较好看
- It's better like that. - Yeah?
帽子太小了
It feels too tight, huh?
是有点小
- Yeah, a little. - Okay.
- 怎么了? - 他们来了
- What? - They're here.
贝蒂 离我愈远愈好 快走
- Betty, look at me, look at me! - Bruce!
你离我远点!
You have to go far away from me as you can!
- 别和我争了 走就是了 快走!
- Don't argue with me, just go. Go!- Bruce!
3分钟后狙击手就会到位
Damn it! We'd have had snipers on target in three more minutes.
是谁擅自行动?
I wanna know who jumped the gun.
他逃向270方位
He's heading 2- 7- 0.
布朗斯基 还不行
Blonsky! Not yet!
长官
Sir.
注意看 这会很有趣
Look alive. This could get interesting.
看到他了
I got him!
停车!停车!
Stop! Stop!
我知道你在里面
I know you're in there!
将军 求求你
General, please!
长官?
Sir?
爸!
Dad!
- 爸 求求你住手 - 你不清楚状况
- Dad, please don't do this. - You can't see this clearly. Now, get inside.
他在那里!
There he is!
目标在天桥
Target is in the overpass. We have a visual.
不要进去
Do not engage! Repeat, do not engage!
他被锁在里面
He's locked in.
发射两枚催泪弹
Put two canisters in there with him.
发射!
Fire!
把她带回来
Get her back here!
她会看清真相
Now she'll see.
A队?
Alpha team?
全力开火
Let him have all of it.
来 干掉他!
Come on, light him up!
50口径火炮呢?快上呀!
Where are the fifty cals? Move your asses!
我的老天!
Oh, my God!
布朗斯基 上吧
Blonsky, now you're up!
长官
Sir?
掩护我
Cover me.
记得我吗?
Remember me?
天啊 他真的变强了
My God, he's doing it.
把他引到音波炮那里
Move him toward the cannons!
启动!
Move!
守好你的位置!
Hold your position!
就现在
Do it now!
求求你住手
Please, please, please, no!
- 求你 - 让她回来
- Please, please, please!- Get her back!
你会杀死他
You're killing him!
住手!放开我!
Stop! Get off of me!
布鲁斯!
Bruce!
Bruce! Bruce!
攻击直升机呢?
Where's the gunship?
就这样?
Is that it?
布朗斯基 撤退!
Blonsky, pull back now.
回来
Pull back!
你就只有这点料吗?
Is that all you got?
- 撤退! - 撤退!
- Fall back! - Fall back! Let's go, let's go!
快找掩护!
Find cover!
贝蒂!
Betty!
快开火呀!
Fire, goddamn it!
布鲁斯?
Bruce?
停火!
Stop firing!
不!
No!
你打给我是对的
You did the right thing, calling us.
我要知道他们去哪里
I need to know where they're going.
她跟他在一起很危险
She'll be in incredible danger as long as she's with him.
谁会伤害她?
From who?
他保护她 你却差点害死她
He protected her. You almost killed her.
我保证 她的安危最重要
I give you my word, her safety is my main concern at this point.
身为精神科医师的我
You know, it's a point of professional pride with me
看得出谁说谎
that I can always tell when somebody's lying.
你在说谎
And you are.
我不知道他去哪里
I don't know where he's going.
- 我只知道她一定会帮他 - 那她就算是协助逃犯
- I know she'll help him, if she can. - Then she's aiding a fugitive.
我也帮不了他们
And I can't help either one of them.
我一直在想她为什么从不提起你
I used to wonder why she never talked about you.
现在我知道原因了
Now I know!
她都在哪里率墩庑┭方
Where does she meet these guys?
布鲁斯?
Bruce?
布鲁斯
Bruce.
没关系 没有事
It's okay. It's okay.
过来 跟我来
Come here. Come this way.
小心头
Watch your head.
我们没事
We're okay.
没事
It's okay.
只是下雨而已
It's just the rain.
他能再走路吗?
Will he ever walk again?
他全身的骨头支离破碎
Most of the bones in his body look like crushed gravel right now.
不过我很佩服他 他的心脏像个机器
I will say this for him. He's got a heart like a machine.
就跟赛马一样强
Never seen anything like it, outside of a racehorse.
来
Here.
布鲁斯?
Bruce?
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
我好多了
Yeah.
事实上 我感觉好多了
Yeah, actually, I feel a lot better.
- 那就好 - 我得把资料拿出来
- Good. - I just had to get my data back.
你把它吃掉?
You ate it?
情况紧急 我总得想办法
Well, you know, the circumstances called for a little improvisation.
款式不多 不过你有一些选择
Okay, so they didn't have a great selection, but I got you some options.
这玩意比较重要
First thing's first.
你在开玩笑吧?
Oh, you're kidding me.
怎么了?
What?
这是最宽松的一件
- No. - They were the stretchiest pair they had.
我宁愿冒险
I'll take my chances.
有关于军队和不明敌人
Rumours continue to swirl about a violent clash
在卡尔弗大学校园发生激烈战斗的谣言
between forces of the US military and an unknown adversary
持续延烧
on the campus of Culver University earlier today.
两名大二学生目击整个事件
Sophomores Jack McGhee and Jim Wilson witnessed some of the battle.
那玩意超大的
It was so big.
就像一个绿色巨人
- It was like this huge, like, hulk! - Yeah.
其中一名学生是校报记者
McGhee, who happens to be a reporter for the campus paper,
他用手机拍下这些画面
captured this on his cell phone.
国家森林下起一阵雷暴雨
Further search for the mysterious "hulk"
神秘绿巨人的搜寻行动因此拖延
was postponed by powerful thunderstorms in the Smoky Mountain National Forest.
"汽车旅馆"
后面不要剪太短
Not too short back there.
我以前帮你剪过头发
I have done this before, you know.
我不知道你自己是怎么剪的
I don't know how you've done this on your own for all this time.
通常都是用电剪
With clippers, usually.
等一下
- Wait, wait, wait. Wait. - What? What?
我们不能这样
We can't do this.
- 没关系 我想要 - 不
- It's okay. I want to. - No.
不
No.
我不行
I can't.
我不能太兴奋
I can't get too excited.
一点点都不行吗?
Not even a little excited?
没关系
It's okay.
长官 是布朗斯基
Sir, it's Blonsky.
他有没有家人?
Has anyone found out if he has next of kin or family?
你自己问他
Ask him yourself.
长官?
Sir?
- 很高兴看到你复原 大兵 - 谢谢你 长官
- Good to see you back on your feet, soldier. - Thank you, sir.
你觉得怎样?
How do you feel?
超不爽的 我要打第三回合
Pissed off and ready for round three.
这些都不能用 会被追踪
Basically, we can't use any of this, because they can track all of it.
我的唇蜜都会被追踪?
Well, my lip gloss? Can they track that?
- 不会 你可以拿去 - 谢了
- No. You can take your lip gloss. - Thank you.
- 我也需要眼镜 - 你也可以
- Well, I need my glasses. - Well, you can take
把眼镜和手表拿去
- your glasses and your watch, okay? - Okay.
大部份都能用 不能用信用卡
We can use most of it. We just can't use the credit cards, the ID or the phone.
手机也别开机
- Don't even turn that on. - Okay.
我们只能用现金
And we'll take the cash, obviously.
光靠四十块钱该怎么逃亡?
How will we get where we need to go on $40 and no credit cards?
我们可以典当这条项链
Well, we could sell this.
不 这是你妈唯一留给你的
No. No, that's the only thing you have left from her. No.
那就一定要赎回来
Well, we'll have to try and get it back.
调查局在监视手机信用卡
Federal is already monitoring phones,plastic and Dr Ross's web accounts,
和罗博士的纲路帐号
and local PD have been placed on alert.
当地警方设下临检站 只要他们出现就会通知我们
They'll pop up somewhere and when they do, it comes straight to us.
他们不会就这样出现
They're not gonna just pop up.
他这五年来一直在各国游走
He made it five years and got across borders without making any mistakes.
绝对不会使用信用卡
He's not gonna use a damn credit card now.
他想逃早就走远了
If he was trying to escape, he'd be long gone.
这次他不准备逃跑了
He's not trying to escape this time.
如果他想找人帮忙我们就能逮到他
He's looking for help and that's how we're gonna get him.
他有和别人联络
We know what they're after and we know he's been talking to somebody.
你们都看过资料
You all have copies of the correspondence.
绿先生和蓝先生的昵称
The aliases Mr Green and Mr Blue
已经加入神盾资料库 标题:绿先生来信
have been added to the SHIELD Operations Database.
蓝先生 资料在这里 该见面了 绿先生
If he comes up for air, we'll be waiting.
他一现身 我们马上知道
If he makes a peep, we'll hear him.
他一出错 我们就会出动
And when he slips up, we'll be ready.
神盾局
后勤部
蓝先生 资料在这里 - 绿先生
格邦学院
细胞生物系
"山缪史登博士" 找到符合项目
找到符合项目
山缪史登博士 纽约
格邦学院
出售
笑一个
Smile.
那是什么感觉?
What is it like?
变身的感觉是什么?
When it happens, what do you experience?
记得我们在哈佛自愿参与的
Remember those experiments we volunteered for at Harvard?
引导幻觉实验吗?
Those induced hallucinations?
就像那样 再放大一千倍
It's a lot like that, just a thousand times amplified.
就像把一公升迷幻药倒进我脑袋
It's like someone's poured a litre of acid into my brain.
- 你记得什么吗? - 只有零星的画面
太多噪音 我什么也分不清楚
There's too much noise. I can never derive anything out of it.
- 那么你还是在它里面 - 并没有
- But then it's still you inside it. - No. No, it's not.
我不晓得 但它在山洞 我觉得它就像知道我一样
I don't know. In the cave, I really felt like it knew me.
也许你的大脑超载
Maybe your mind is in there,
失去控制
it's just overcharged and can't process what's happening.
我不想控制它 我想消灭它
I don't want to control it. I want to get rid of it.
准备好了吗?
Are you ready?
这样才旗鼓相当
Let's even the playing field a little.
开始了
Gentlemen.
布鲁斯 醒醒 情况不妙
Bruce, wake up. There's something going on.
前有路障
准备停车
我们得下车 慢慢往后面走
We got to go. Walk toward the back. Just don't move too fast.
好了 来吧
All right. Come.
到上城很远 坐地铁应该最快
It is a long way uptown. I think the subway's probably quickest.
我和几百个人挤在车厢
Me in a metal tube, deep underground,
肯定会被逼到抓狂
with hundreds of people in the most aggressive city in the world?
没错 咱们坐计程车
Right. Let's get a cab.
拜托!快点!你开车像个娘儿们!
Come on, now! Let's go! You're too slow! You drive like a woman!
看到没?一个大美女
- Very nice. You see her? - Oh, my.
你有没有长眼睛呀?
Very pretty. Watch out, you goat!
呼吸 呼吸
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
你疯了吗?
Are you out of your mind?
怎么?
- What is wrong with you? - What's the matter, baby?
你不喜欢飙车?
You don't like a good ride?
大混球
Asshole!
我可以教你怎么控制怒气
You know, I know a few techniques could help you
闭嘴 走吧
- manage that anger very effectively. - You zip it. We're walking.
对不起 史登博士?
Excuse me. Dr Sterns?
我是伊莉莎白罗斯
- Yes. - I'm sorry to bother you. I'm Elizabeth Ross.
罗斯博士!
Oh! Dr Ross!
- 有人想要见你 - 好
- I have someone who'd like to meet you. - Okay.
蓝先生?
It's Mr Blue, isn't it?
绿先生?
Mr Green?
我一直在猜你是不是真有其人
I got to tell you, I've been wondering if you were even real.
如果是 你长什么样子
And if you were, what would it look like?
一个蕴藏着这么强大力量的人
A person with that much power lurking in him.
竟然像你这么不起眼
Nothing could have surprised me more
让我大吃一惊
than this unassuming man shaking my hand.
这并不简单...
But, look. We're not strolling into the park for a picnic, here.
就算一切都顺利
Even if everything goes perfectly,
引导你变身后注射正确剂量
if we induce an episode, if we get the dosage exactly right,
你会永远被治愈...
is that going to be a lasting cure
...或者只是暂时被压制而已?
or just some antidote to suppress that specific flare- up?
我也不知道
I don't know.
要是注射的剂量稍微多一点
What I'm saying is that if we overshoot this by even the smallest integer
就会出现高成份的毒性
we're dealing with concentrations with extraordinary levels of toxicity.
- 可能会害死他 - 当然了 我敢肯定
- You mean it could kill him. - Kill him? Yeah. I should say so.
也可能完全相反
You should know that there's a flip side to this, too.
要是剂量太少 无法压制我
If we miss on the low side, if we induce me and it fails,
你就会陷入危险
this will be very dangerous for you.
我一向都是个好奇宝宝
Look. I've always been more curious than cautious,
从来没出过事 到底要不要做呀?
and that's served me pretty well. So, are we going to do this?
你有什么感觉?
How you feeling, man?
像个怪物
Like a monster.
好了 躺上去
Okay. On the table.
万一你有强烈反应 这能保护你自己
These will protect you from yourself if you have a strong reaction.
等你觉得太强烈再告诉我
You can tell me later if you thought it was strong.
拜托 那些蠢研究生
Oh, come on! Stupid graduate students.
你 你 你
You, you, you.
这会是很新奇的感觉
This will be a somewhat novel sensation.
我们开始了
We have begun.
血液析离器会混和解药和你的血液
The dialysis machine will mix the antidote with your blood.
但你要完全变身解药才会起作用
Except the antidote will only take hold once we've achieved a full reaction.
放轻松
Just relax.
好了 作业完成
Okay. We are comprehensive.
拿去
Here you go.
好了 准备好了吗?
All right. We set to pop?
你最好别碰他
I'd take your hands off him.
我的老天!
Oh, my God!
等等 还没结束
Wait, wait! There's more! Wait!
- 现在 现在! - 等一下
- Now. Okay, now! - Wait.
快点!快点!
Now, do it! Do it!
布鲁斯 看着我
Bruce! Bruce, look at me.
快注射解药 史登 快呀!
Stay with me. The antidote, now! Sterns, do it now!
布鲁斯 看着我的眼睛
Bruce, look at me. Look in my eyes. Please, look in my eyes.
这一定是开玩笑
Oh, you've got to be kidding me!
布鲁斯
Bruce.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
布鲁斯?你听得见吗?
Bruce? Bruce, can you hear me?
布鲁斯?
Bruce?
没事了 你没事了
It's okay. You're okay. You're okay.
你撑过去了
You did it.
他没事 太棒了
He's fine. This is fantastic.
结束了
It's over.
那是我这辈子见过最惊人的事
That was the most extraordinary thing I have seen in my entire life!
别这么兴奋
Okay, you know what? Stop, please.
我们得讨论刚才发生的事
We need to go back and talk about what just happened in there.
没问题 伽玛脉冲来自大脑的杏仁核
Absolutely. Okay. The gamma pulse came from the amygdala.
- 我想是罗斯博士的核酸链 - 你还好吗?
- I think Dr Ross's primer...- Are you okay?
核酸链让你的细胞暂时吸收能量 过一阵子能量就减退
...lets the cells absorb the energy temporarily, and then it abates.
所以你多年前才没死于辐射病
That's why you didn't die of radiation sickness years ago!
我们也许中和了这些细胞
Now, maybe we've neutralised those cells permanently,
或者只是压制这次变身
or maybe we just suppressed that event.
我猜是后者吧 但是我不确定
I'm inclined to think the latter, but it's hard to know
我的实验样本从来没有存活
because none of our test subjects ever survived.
- 当然 他们没有得到核酸链 - 等等
- Of course, they weren't getting the primer! - Wait, wait.
- 慢着, 你说什么? - 它们没有吸收
- Wait, what did you just say?- They weren't getting
- 核酸链 - 不 不 实验样本?
- the myostatin primer...- No, no, no. Test subjects?
什么实验样本?
What test subjects?
跟我来
Come with me.
- 布署得如何? - 狙击手负责A区
- What's the activity level? - Snipers are covering Alpha sector.
我们先用白老鼠做实验
We started on rats and mice,
但是都死掉 于是得用大型动物
but it just completely fried them, so we had to go bigger.
我不确定是伽玛或是你的血比较毒
And we still don't know which is more toxic, the gamma or your blood.
- 什么意思? - 这全都是你的血
- What do you mean, my blood? - Bruce, this is all you.
你寄给我的并不多 于是我浓缩以后又制造更多
You didn't send me much to work with, so I had to concentrate it and make more.
只要继续研究就有无限的可能
With a little more trial and error, there's no end to what we can do!
无穷的潜力
This is potentially Olympian!
这种伽玛科技有数不尽的用途
This gamma technology has limitless applications.
我们能发现数百种解药
We'll unlock hundreds of cures.
让人类对各种疾病完全免疫
We will make humans impervious to disease!
不 我们得销毁它
No, no, we've got to destroy it.
- 什么?- 所有
- Wait, what? - All of it.
今晚就得把这一切烧毁
Tonight. We're gonna incinerate it.
- 这里的所有? - 什么
- Is this the whole supply? - What...
我们可以得到诺贝尔奖耶!
We could get the Nobel for this!
你不知道这东西的力量
You don't understand the power of this thing.
太危险了 无法控制
It is too dangerous. It cannot be controlled.
看到目标就开枪
At your discretion, shooter.
我们三个!这是普罗米修斯的圣火!
three of us!This is Promethean fire!
仅仅
It's just...
瞄不准
No shot.
布朗斯基进去了
Blonsky's going in.
不准进去 我女儿在里头
Blonsky, stand down. My daughter's in there!
我们有解药
We have the antidote now.
他们只想把它当成武器
They don't want the antidote! They want to make it a weapon!
如果它被政府抢走就完了
And if we let it go, we will never get it back.
你不知道它的力量有多强大
You don't know how powerful this thing is.
我也讨厌政府
I hate the government just as much as anyone,
不过你也未免太紧张了
but you're being a little paranoid, don't you think?
布鲁斯!布鲁斯!
Bruce! Bruce!
快走
Get out.
它在哪里?
Where is it? Come on, where is it?
让它现身
Show him to me.
布朗斯基!
Blonsky!
小姐
Miss!
披着吧
Take this.
你敢消灭浩克就得一辈子坐牢
If you took it from me, I'm gonna put you in a hole for the rest of your life.
贝蒂
Betty.
我永远不会原谅你这么对他
I will never forgive what you've done to him.
他是个逃犯
He's a fugitive.
是你逼他成为逃犯
You made him a fugitive
为了掩饰你的失败和保护你自己
to cover your failures and to protect your career.
我不屑再当你的女儿
Don't ever speak to me as your daughter again.
如果你不是我女儿也会被捕
It's only because you're my daughter that you're not in handcuffs, too.
你能打造出更多浩克?
Are you telling me you can make more like him?
还不行 我有一些资料
No! Not yet. I sorted out a few pieces, but it's not like I can put together
但是还不能复制出同样的巨人
the same Humpty Dumpty, if that's what you're asking.
浩克纯粹是个意外 我的目标是要做得更好
He was a freak accident! The goal is to do it better!
班纳是唯一的...
So Banner's the only...
- 她真的很烦人 - 你为什么老是在打人?
- She's an annoying bitch. - Why are you always hitting people?
我到底是做了什么惹毛了你?
Now what possibly could I have done to deserve such aggression?
不是你做的事 是你要做的事
It's not what you've done. It's what you're gonna do.
我要你从班纳身上提炼的东西
I want what you got out of Banner. I want that.
看来你已经注射了一些东西
You look like you've got a little something in you already, don't you?
我要更多 你也看到他变成浩克
I want more. You've seen what he becomes, right?
没错
I have.
它太美了
And it's beautiful.
就像神一样
Godlike.
我也要变成那样
Well, I want that.
你要把我变成那样
I need that. Make me that.
我不知道你体内有什么
I don't know what you've got inside you already.
混在一起可能变成
The mix could be
一个大祸害
an abomination.
我没说我不愿意
I didn't say I was unwilling.
我只是需要你的同意
I just need informed consent.
你也同意了
And you've given it.
"绿先生-效力14.56%"
这就是我想跟你解释的事
This is what I was trying to explain.
我不知道你注射了什么东西
I don't know what you've been ladling into yourself.
但是很明显起了效用
But clearly it worked.
我假设你完全听不懂我的话
Let's assume you don't understand a word I'm saying,
不过还是请你躺回去
but if you'll just get back on the table,
好让我把你治好
I can fix this.
- 开枪! - 嘿
Shoot it! - Hey!
不
No!
D4呼叫队长
Delta 4 to Leader.
他们杀死我们两名弟兄
They took out two of our guys, two of our guys!
布朗斯基和中校还在里头
Blonsky and the Major are still inside!
快点!快走!
Come on! Move, move, move, move!
它在那里!
It's over there!
离开他们
Drop them!
- 那是什么东西? - 向它开枪!
What is that thing? - Shoot it!
你开车!快!快走!
Okay. All right! You... You, drive! Let's go! Move, move!
队长
Delta 4 to Leader! - Go, go, go, go, go!
有个大怪物从这里逃走
Something big just went off down here!
将军 你最好听听看
General, you should hear this!
浩克在街上!重复 浩克在街上!
The Hulk is in the street! I repeat, the Hulk is in the street!
不可能 先冷静下来
That's impossible. You get a hold of yourself, young man.
你在哪里?
You get it together. What is your position?
121街和北向百老汇路口
121st Street, heading north on Broadway!
快掉头
Turn us around.
我们为什么要回去?
We're going back. Why are we going back?
给我影像
Damn it! Give me eyes down there!
是 长官
Yes, sir!
那是什么东西?
What the hell was that?
快 快
Go, go, go!
不!
No!
你的实验品吗?
One of yours?
天啊 你做了什么?
Oh, my God. What have you done?
开火!开火!
Fire at him, fire at him!
你想它怕子弹吗?
Do you think a rifle's gonna hurt that?
走吧!
Come on!
水喔
Sweet.
赶快撤退!
Get out of there, soldier!
给我更强的对手
Give me a real fight!
长官?
Sir?
下令把所有军力调到哈林区
Tell them to bring everything they've got and head for Harlem.
让我去 你一定要让我去
It has to be me. You have to take me back there.
你在说什么?
What are you saying?
你以为你能控制它?
You think you can control it?
不是控制 而是利用它
No, no, not control it, but, I don't know, maybe aim it.
要是不行呢?
And what if you can't?
这东西是我们创造出来的
We made this thing.
我们所有人
All of us.
求求你
Please.
- 降落在它附近 - 不 留在高空
- Land us near it. - No, no. No, keep us high.
打开后舱门
Open the back door.
布鲁斯 站住 你在做什么?
Bruce! Bruce, stop! Stop! What are you doing?
你要想清楚 你不知道自己会不会变身
Think about this! You don't even know if you'll change!
别这么做 太疯狂了
You don't have to do this! Please, this is insane!
贝蒂 我得试一试
Betty, I've got to try.
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 把她拉进来 - 来吧 小姐
- Get her in here! - Come on, miss.
贝蒂 它在那里
There. Betty!
浩克!
Hulk!
太好了!
Yeah!
来吧!
Come on!
你只有这点料吗?
Is that all you've got?
快用机关枪!帮助他!
Use that thing, soldier! Give him some help!
帮哪一个?
Which one?
绿色的那一个
Help the green one, damn it! Which one do you think?
把另一个射死
Cut the other one in half!
罗斯!
Ross!
继续开火!
Keep it on him!
- 我得紧急迫降 - 抓紧了!
Look, I got to put it down! - Hang on!
爸?
Dad?
你没事吧?我来帮你
Are you hurt? Let me help you.
我没事 快想办法出去
I'm all right. Just find a way out.
你不配拥有这种力量 眼睁睁看她死吧!
You don't deserve this power! Now watch her die!
小心!
Look out!
将军?
General?
你有遗言吗?
Any last words?
浩克出击!
Hulk smash!
住手!
Stop!
没事了
It's okay.
贝蒂
Betty.
"低电量"
贝拉库拉 加拿大卑诗省
"寄件人:米尔本当铺"
贝蒂罗斯-卡尔弗大学
距离上次变身-第31天
距离上次变身-第0天
再来一杯
Reload.
走气啤酒和失败的味道
The smell of stale beer and defeat.
我早就告诉过你了
You know, I hate to say, "I told you so," General,
超级大兵计划被终止不是没原因
but that Super Soldier programme was put on ice for a reason.
我一向觉得硬体比较可靠
I've always felt hardware was more reliable.
- 史塔克 - 将军
- Stark. - General.
你总是穿得光鲜亮丽
You always wear such nice suits.
说得好
Touch?
- 听说你有个不寻常的问题 - 你不用说我也知道
- I hear you have an unusual problem. - You should talk.
听我说
You should listen.
我们正在组织一个联盟
What if I told you we were putting a team together?
"我们"是谁?
Who's "we"?